<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8' standalone='no'?>
<doxygen xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="compound.xsd" version="1.8.16">
  <compounddef id="indexpage" kind="page">
    <compoundname>index</compoundname>
    <title>Texas Aerial Robotics</title>
    <briefdescription>
    </briefdescription>
    <detaileddescription>
<para>This site host the documentation for our projects.</para>
<para><heading level="2">Documentation</heading>
</para>
<para><ref refid="md_linux_commands" kindref="compound">Common Linux Commands</ref> - This document contains a list of common linux commands</para>
<para><ref refid="md_enviorment_setup" kindref="compound">Enviroment Setup Instructions</ref> - This document explains how to setup our development enviorment</para>
<para><ref refid="md_basic_ros" kindref="compound">Robot Operating System (ROS)</ref> - This document links to helpful tutorials to help you learn ROS</para>
<para><ref refid="md_basic_gazebo" kindref="compound">Gazebo</ref> - This document links to helpful tutorials to help you learn ROS</para>
<para><ref refid="md_arducopter" kindref="compound">ArduCopter</ref> - This gives a quick rundown on arducopter</para>
<para><ref refid="md_control_api_tutorial" kindref="compound">Control API</ref> - This document explains how to code our drone to move</para>
<para><ref refid="md_yolo" kindref="compound">YOLO Image Recognition</ref> - This document explains how to use YOLO (You Only Look Once, a realtime image detection neural net)</para>
<para><ref refid="md_yoloTraining" kindref="compound">Training YOLO with BBox-Label-Tool</ref> - This document explains how to train YOLO to recognize your own objects</para>
<para><ref refid="md_yolo_ros" kindref="compound">Using YOLO with ROS</ref> - This package explains how to integrate yolo into your robot architecture using ROS</para>
<para><ref refid="md_monocular_uav" kindref="compound">Object Contextualization with Monocular Camera for a UAV</ref> - This package is designed to work hand in hand with YOLO and Ardupilot to give the UAV awareness of where detected objects are in the UAV&apos;s navigational frame. </para>
    </detaileddescription>
  </compounddef>
</doxygen>
